<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Kento Nakamura</title>
    <link>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Kento Nakamura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 23:41:32 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 23:41:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/links/</guid>
      <description> Labeoratory for Quantitative Biology Institute of Industrial Science Department of Mathematical Informatics Graduate school of Information Science and Technology the University of Tokyo </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 23:49:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education March 2023
Ph. D. of Information Science and Technology at Department of Mathematical Informatics, Graduate school of Information Science and Technology, the University of Tokyo
Supervisor: Prof. Tetsuya J. Kobayashi
Thesis: Mathematical analysis of dynamic cellular decision-making based on optimality theory
March 2020
Master of Information Science and Technology from Department of Mathematical Informatics, Graduate school of Information Science and Technology, the University of Tokyo
Supervisor: Prof. Tetsuya J. Kobayashi</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 23:47:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kento-nakamura.netlify.app/page/publications/</guid>
      <description>Journal Papers (Refereed) Kento Nakamura and Tetsuya J. Kobayashi
Optimal sensing and control of run-and-tumble chemotaxis
Physical Review Research, 4, 013120, 2022. [journal] Kento Nakamura and Tetsuya J. Kobayashi
Connection between the bacterial chemotactic network and optimal filtering
Physical Review Letters, 126, 128102, 2021. [journal] [arXiv] Kento Nakamura, Keisuke Yano, and Fumiyasu Komaki
Adjacency-based regularization for partially ranked data with non-ignorable missing
Computational Statistics &amp;amp; Data Analysis, 145, 106905, 2020. [journal] International conferences Oral presentation Kento Nakamura, Keisuke Yano, and Fumiyasu Komaki</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
